A Guide to the James Hinkle-William Faulkner Research Collection
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Articles re Faulkner's Novels and Short Stories (Othertype 4)
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Tomorrow," Text 1940 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Two Soldiers" 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Uncle Willy," and Text 1935, 1978 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Vendee," Text 1936 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"The Waifs," Text 1957 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--War Stories 1954-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Wash," and Text 1934, 1963-1970 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - "Miss Zilphia Gant," and Text 1932, 1954-1975 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: The Snopes Triology 1958-1982, 4 folders (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: The Snopes Triology--"The Hamlet" 1941-1988, 5 folders (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: The Snopes Triology--"The Mansion" 1959-1982 (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: The Snopes Triology--"The Town" 1957-1989 (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: Soldier's Pay 1979-1980 (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: The Sound and the Fury 1939-1967, 6 folders (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: The Unvanquished 1952-1983, 3 folders (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: The Wild Palms1980 (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
- Articles re Faulkner Miscellaneous (Othertype 2)
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous 1931-1957, 5 folders (Othertype 10 (A25-16B))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous 1958-1959 (Othertype 11 (A25-16C))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous 1960-1969, 9 folders (Othertype 11 (A25-16C))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous 1970-1977, 7 folders (Othertype 11 (A25-16C))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous 1978-1979 (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous 1980-1988, 3 folders (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous--Interviews with Faulkner 1951-1964 (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous--Reminiscences of Faulkner 1932-1984, 3 folders (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Faulkner Miscellaneous--Reviews of Books on Faulkner 1964-1984 (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Hemingway Misecellaneous 1978-1988, 2 folders (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
- Articles re Southern History (Othertype 2)
  - Articles: Southern History 1835-1899 (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Southern History 1900-1909, 4 folders (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Southern History 1910-1919 (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Southern History 1921-1929, 2 folders (Othertype 12-(A25-16D))
  - Articles: Southern History 1930-1932, 2 folders (Othertype 12 (A25-16D))
  - Articles: Southern History 1933-1939, 4 folders (Othertype 13 (A25-16E))
  - Articles: Southern History 1940-1948, 6 folders (Othertype 13 (A25-16E))
  - Articles: Southern History 1949-1958, 8 folders (Othertype 13 (A25-16E))
  - Articles: Southern History 1959 (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
  - Articles: Southern History 1960-1969, 7 folders (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
  - Articles: Southern History 1970-1979, 7 folders (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
  - Articles: Southern History 1980-1988, n.d., 4 folders (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
  - Articles: Southern History--Mississippi 1919-1962, 3 folders [from The Oxford Eagle] (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
- Concordance, 109 linear feet (Othertype Card file)
- Mississippi: Map--Geological Surveys by U.S. Geological Survey 1912, Oversize (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
- Mississippi: Maps--Geological Surveys by U.S. Geological Survey 1940, 1942, oversize (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))
- Mississippi: Maps--Sedimentation Surveys by U.S. Army Corp of Engineers 1951, oversize (Othertype 14 (A25-16F))